Margaret Cooper
DC Public Library Special Collections
Margaret Cooper Papers
1927-1997
DC Public Library, Special Collections
15 cubic feet; 5 boxes
133
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Queen Esther Household of Ruth, 1927-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Environment, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Community (1 of 2), 1978-1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Community (2 of 2), 1969-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Shaw Community/ANC, 1982-1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Scouts, 1976-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1956-1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - DHCD Housing Programs, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Africare, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Christian Endeavor Songs, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Lott Carey Baptist Herald, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - New Samaritan Baptist Church, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Payne Memorial African Methodist Church Annual Conference Program, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Baptist Sunday Union of Washington and Vicinity, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Third Baptist Church Bulletins, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Third Baptist Church Bulletins, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Third Baptist Church Bulletins, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Third Baptist Church Bulletins, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Christian Endeavor Night Tickets, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Certificates/Awards/Nominations (1 of 4), 1954-1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Certificates/Awards/Nominations (2 of 4), 1954-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Certificates/Awards/Nominations (3 of 4), 1954-1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Certificates/Awards/Nominations (4 of 4), 1954-1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Dues Cards and Donation Envelope, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Mid City Tenants Action Council - Urban Renewal Area, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Buttons, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Marjorie Webster Junior College, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Certificates of Appreciation, 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Certificate of Election, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Photographs (1 of 2), undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photographs (2 of 2), undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stickers, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1949-1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Speeches, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Constitution of the Third Baptist Church, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - DC Statehood, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Song Lyrics, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Programs, 1948-1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters and History, 1983-1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Salutes and Tributes to Margaret Cooper, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Greeting Cards, 1964-1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The Standard Leadership Curriculum and Course Card of Recognition, 1955-1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Fauntroy Calender and Business Card, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Resolution, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Diamond Award from United to Serve America, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - DC Department of Public Works Posters, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Crime Solvers Posters, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Office of the Mayor DC Proclamation, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - DC Council Resolution, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - DC Council Resolution, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - DC Council Resolution, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)